{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
      "question": "In the Hellboy universe, what was Abe Sapien&#039;s birth name?",
      "correct_answer": "Langdon Everett Caul",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Lord Baltimore",
        "Sir Edward Grey",
        "Landis Pope"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
      "question": "When Batman trolls the online chat rooms, what alias does he use?",
      "correct_answer": "JonDoe297",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "iAmBatman",
        "BWayne13",
        "BW1129"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
      "question": "In 1978, Superman teamed up with what celebrity, to defeat an alien invasion?",
      "correct_answer": "Muhammad Ali",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Mike Tyson",
        "Sylvester Stallone",
        "Arnold Schwarzenegger"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
      "question": "What are the names of the two &quot;Canon fan trolls&quot; in &quot;Homestuck&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Mierfa Durgas and Nektan Whelan",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The Wrycrown and Voksea Olkido",
        "Aikter Frekik and Xagrai Ollomu",
        "Grekei Ceknux and Riya Camacho"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
      "question": "Better known by his nickname Logan, what is Wolverine&#039;s birth name?",
      "correct_answer": "James Howlett",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Logan Wolf",
        "Thomas Wilde",
        "John Savage"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
      "question": "What is the real hair colour of the mainstream comic book version (Earth-616) of Daredevil?",
      "correct_answer": "Blonde",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Auburn",
        "Brown",
        "Black"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
      "question": "Which of the following rings from the DC Comics&#039; &quot;Lantern Corps&quot; are classified as Parasitic?",
      "correct_answer": "Indigo (Compassion)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Green (Willpower)",
        "White (Life)",
        "Yellow (Fear)"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
      "question": "Which pulp hero made appearances in Hellboy and BPRD comics before getting his own spin-off?",
      "correct_answer": "Lobster Johnson",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Roger the Homunculus",
        "The Spider",
        "The Wendigo"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
      "question": "In the &quot;Archie&quot; comics, who was Jughead&#039;s first girlfriend?",
      "correct_answer": "Joani",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ethel",
        "Debbi",
        "Margret"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
      "question": "In the webcomic &quot;Ava&#039;s Demon&quot;, what sin is &quot;Nevy Nervine&quot; based off of? ",
      "correct_answer": "Envy ",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Sloth",
        "Wrath ",
        "Lust"
      ]
    }
  ]
}